Yakanta Idol
Okay, now let's get to the main project of this YouTube!
The theme of this YouTube is "cute", so please call the title rapidly!
My 3 main elements
Yay!
This is a corner where we ask you about the 3 main elements that make you Rinasan!
Now, please announce the three elements.
Here are my 3 main elements that make me who I am.
Okay, I'll read from the top.
Can I ask you to read three?
The first one is the one I don't know yet.
Number two is appropriate.
The third one is the one you're into, and it's loud.
Who's the one you don't know yet?
This one?
Well, this one, I'm interested in things I've never done before.
Oh...
Yes, I'm very adventurous.
So you are very curious.
Yes, I'm interested in playing the guitar and cooking.
I have this great desire to start.
Yes, yes.
Yes, I'm very quick to take action.
I see. Let's give it a try first.
Yes, let's try it first.
Wow.
Is there anything you've done recently that you're directly interested in?
Well, I'm going to go to Pilates this month.
You're going? From now on?
I've already made an appointment, so I'll go now.
Is Pilates like yoga?
It's like yoga.
It's a little more like a muscle training version of yoga.
I see.
Yes, it is.
I've heard that it's really good for people who do Pilates.
You've experienced it?
Yes, that's right.
I see.
So, yes, I have recently been studying Pilates, which I don't know yet.
Pilates
Is there anything else you'd like to try?
I'm also interested in musical instruments.
Besides guitar, I'm also interested in drums and other instruments.
Do you play guitar?
I played a song at a birthday party a while ago.
That's right.
But I also played the drums when I was in elementary school.
My teacher taught me how to play the drums when I was in elementary school.
Uh-huh.
I used to play during free time and recess.
Oh, really?
Yes, that's right. I've been thinking about starting recently.
Wow.
That kind of desire to challenge yourself is what makes up who you are, isn't it?
Yes, I do.
But what you are doing now, Pilates...
That has something to do with your work, doesn't it?
Yes, that's right. Crapo's dance is quite intense.
So I thought it was important to have a sense of it.
I see.
I'd like to try something that has nothing to do with work.
Well, well, I don't know if there's any eventual draw out.
But personally, I'd like to try bungee jumping.
Oh! No bungee?
No, I don't.
Something like that.
I'm sure we can make this happen soon.
Oh, really?
Yes, sir.
Yes, I'm sure.
Mirabungee Challenge
I'd like to try it.
I can't even imagine what it would be like.
I'm curious to try something I can't imagine.
Bungee
I'd like to try something else.
I'd like to open a koten or something.
I don't know...
I'm not that good at drawing.
I'm not that good at drawing, but I like photography.
I like to take pictures.
You have one of these? Photographs from your college classes?
Yes, I do.
Like a video camera... even if I'm not in society.
Even if I'm not in society.
You mean I should know about it?
That's right.
I'm going to have my picture taken.
Both the person having their picture taken and the person taking the picture.
Isn't that kind of nice?
Yes, it is.
It's something that could be done now.
It could be done digitally.
It could even be done on the Internet.
I'd like to take a look.
I'm going to do all the research and go out there by myself.
What? Really? So you're core-active?
That's right.
What's this program about?
Mr. Kogezaka.
Mr. Tact
Mr. Katsu
Mr. Ukyou
Mr. Fukazawa
Thank you very much!
Let's see what kind of lilas we can see next time!